<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Cutscenes>
	<scene id="0">
    <bg type="bg"></bg>
    <IntroComplete type="switch" value="true"></IntroComplete>
    <Shadow type="dialog">I see the grassland and the natural setting in front of me. I have arrived in the region of Cindara. I heard that this is an area of peace and solitude for the most part. These people stayed out of the way of others as much as possible. Maybe, I will find reprieve here...</Shadow>
    <Shadow type="party" value="add"></Shadow>
    <Rin type="party" value="add"></Rin>
    <Johnathan type="party" value="add"></Johnathan>
    <Shadow type="ability" value="add" spell="Poison Shot"></Shadow>
    <potion type="item" quantity="1" itemType="consumable"></potion>
    <explore type="next" id="Grassland"></explore>
  </scene>
	<scene id="1">
    <theme type="bgm" value="on"></theme>
    <theme type="bgm" value="off"></theme>
    <Rin type="move" x="3" y="7"></Rin>
    <Rin type="dialog">Hi, are you a traveller? it is rare to see visitors in general here.</Rin>
    <Shadow type="dialog">Yes, I have been travelling for a while, is there a town nearby?</Shadow>
    <Rin type="dialog">There is, I would be happy to guide you there!</Rin>
    <Shadow type="dialog">That is much appreciated, I didnt get your name though?</Shadow>
    <Rin type="dialog">It's Rin, you?</Rin>
    <Shadow type="dialog">Shadow.</Shadow>
    <Rin type="dialog">Let us go then, Shadow?</Rin>
    <Shadow type="dialog">Yes, I might just be on the verge of exhaustion.</Shadow>
    <Rin type="dialog">Alright, the village is just right of here then go up to reach there.</Rin>
    <Notice type="dialog">Rin has joined your party.</Notice>
    <x type="next"></x>
  </scene>
  <scene id="2">
    <Rin type="dialog">I thought you were in a hurry? Let's go! Just head right then up and we will be at the village</Rin>
    <Attacker type="object" value="remove" name="Assassin"></Attacker>
    <x type="next"></x>
  </scene>
  <scene id="3">
    <Rin type="dialog">the town is just up ahead. Let us go</Rin>
    <Shadow type="dialog">Something is coming from that bush!</Shadow>
    <Attacker type="object" value="add" gid="262" x="2" y="6"></Attacker>
    <syndra type="dialog">Watch out!</syndra>
    <Rin type="dialog">Let me give you a battle primer, just in case although i suspect you are a battle veteran anyway.</Rin>
    <Rin type="dialog">There are four commands : Attack, spell, Defend, Item.</Rin>
    <Rin type="dialog">Attack: A physical attack that is based on the character's Attack and is reduced by physical resistance and Defense</Rin>
    <Rin type="dialog">Spell: These range from healing to stats boosters or reducers or Damage skills which is the most common. Experiment and see what works for you.</Rin>
    <Rin type="dialog">Defend: Reduces damage by 33% of any attack done to character defending. Only applies to the first attack and not all attacks for that turn</Rin>
    <Rin type="dialog">Item: Use items for varying effects to turn the tide of battle. Feel free to use your items as you will get more as you go along.</Rin>
    <Rin type="dialog">With that said, I am sure you will figure out the rest! let us go!</Rin>
    <Attacker type="object" value="remove"></Attacker>
    <battle type="next" id="0"></battle>
  </scene>
  <scene id="4">
    <Rin type="dialog">Let me give you a battle primer, just in case although i suspect you are a battle veteran anyway.</Rin>
    <Rin type="dialog">There are four commands : Attack, spell, Defend, Item.</Rin>
    <Rin type="dialog">Attack: A physical attack that is based on the character's Attack and is reduced by physical resistance and Defense</Rin>
    <Rin type="dialog">Spell: These range from healing to stats boosters or reducers or Damage skills which is the most common. Experiment and see what works for you.</Rin>
    <Rin type="dialog">Defend: Reduces damage by 33% of any attack done to character defending. Only applies to the first attack and not all attacks for that turn</Rin>
    <Rin type="dialog">Item: Use items for varying effects to turn the tide of battle. Feel free to use your items as you will get more as you go along.</Rin>
    <Rin type="dialog">With that said, I am sure you will figure out the rest! let us go!</Rin>
    <x type="next"></x>
  </scene>
  <scene id="5">
    <Rin type="dialog">I wonder what was that about...</Rin>
    <Shadow type="dialog">Was that something normal around here?</Shadow>
    <Rin type="dialog">Yeah, around here anyway. I heard neighbouring towns have been experiencing strange attacks. Looks like it finally reached us.</Rin>
    <Shadow type="dialog">That's some relief for me.</Shadow>
    <Rin type="dialog">What?!</Rin>
    <Shadow type="dialog">Don't worry about it, do you know anything more about these strange attackers?</Shadow>
    <Rin type="dialog">...Not much more. I need to talk to the mayor. let us go into the village.</Rin>
    <Shadow type="dialog">yes, that sounds fine.</Shadow>
    <explore type="next" id="Timor"></explore>
  </scene>
  <scene id="6">
    <Mayor type="object" value="add" gid="262" x="5" y="6"></Mayor>
    <Mayor type="dialog">Rin, you have returned.</Mayor>
    <Rin type="dialog">Yes Mayor, did something happen?</Rin>
    <Mayor type="dialog">Yes, Euclid was attacked two days ago by those strange attackers</Mayor>
    <Rin type="dialog">We were attacked as I was leading Shadow here as well</Rin>
    <Mayor type="dialog">What! thank goodness you are safe. I am sorry, Shadow. It is nice to meet you.</Mayor>
    <Shadow type="dialog">Don't worry about it, I would like to know more about these monsters though.</Shadow>
    <Rin type="dialog">You mentioned something about being relieved that we were attacked?</Rin>
    <Mayor type="dialog">!</Mayor>
    <Shadow type="dialog">No, you misunderstood what I mean or rather I said it poorly. I was cursed by someone with dark magic and I thought it might have had something to do with that. When i realized that it was something else, I was relieved.</Shadow>
    <Rin type="dialog">I see...I am sorry for jumping to assumptions</Rin>
    <Shadow type="dialog">That is fine, I did not communicate that well. Mayor, could you tell me more about these Attackers?</Shadow>
    <Mayor type="dialog">We do not know that much about them, the attacks started about a month ago and has become more and more frequently than before.</Mayor>
    <Shadow type="dialog">They have hit various towns, right? if so, was there a pattern in which they were hit? and are the towns already hit, still being hit?</Shadow>
    <Rin type="dialog">Yes they have hit about 5 or 6 towns so far since the initial attack a month ago. As for a pattern, I never thought to look at that.</Rin>
    <Mayor type="dialog">also, all the targetted towns have not been hit again yet, so we dont know their motives</Mayor>
    <Shadow type="dialog">I should have asked this first but what was taken or how much casualities occured at each?</Shadow>
    <Mayor type="dialog">It varies from each attack to the next, I cannot recall there being any common event with all of them.</Mayor>
    <Shadow type="dialog">Could you get me those data for me to look through?</Shadow>
    <Rin type="dialog">We do have the letters we got from a few I think, the rest we only heard got attacked...</Rin>
    <Shadow type="dialog">Could you get those to me by tomorrow please?</Shadow>
    <Mayor type="dialog">Why does this interest you so much though?</Mayor>
    <Shadow type="dialog">I am here and I am capable. I do not believe I need a reason to try to help. It is up to you if you want to trust me though.</Shadow>
    <Mayor type="dialog">Well, you are offering help and we need it. I guess I dont see the issue</Mayor>
    <Shadow type="dialog">Thank you. I need to get some rest now.</Shadow>
    <Rin type="dialog">I will lead you to the inn...</Rin>
    <dialog type="next" id="7"></dialog>
  </scene>
  <scene id="7">
    <Shadow type="dialog">Alright, you got the information?</Shadow>
    <Rin type="dialog">here you go</Rin>
    <Notice type="dialog">A few minutes later...</Notice>
    <Shadow type="dialog">It is no good, this is only 2 of the attacks and there is barely any details in them. Maybe I would have to travel to each of the towns to find out.</Shadow>
    <Rin type="dialog">The Capital would probably be a good place to go, I think they might have some information that would help atleast</Rin>
    <Shadow type="dialog">Could you tell me where it is?</Shadow>
    <Rin type="dialog">I am willing to lead you there if the Mayor is fine with it.</Rin>
    <Shadow type="dialog">Let us go then. There is some stuff I wanted to ask you anyway so you coming along would be cool.</Shadow>
    <Explore type="next" id="Timor"></Explore>
  </scene>
  <scene id="8">
    <Mayor type="dialog">Going to the capital? well, We will be fine here. You can go along.</Mayor>
    <Rin type="dialog">You didnt even think about it! Maybe I won't come back then...</Rin>
    <Mayor type="dialog">Hahaha, alright then, PLEASE DONT GO!!!! HOW WILL I SURVIVE WITHOUT YOU?!</Mayor>
    <Mayor type="dialog">Better?</Mayor>
    <Rin type="dialog">Thanks, thats better...shows your more youthful side!</Rin>
    <Mayor type="dialog">haha, I am still young, you know!</Mayor>
    <Shadow type="dialog">I don't even...</Shadow>
    <Rin type="dialog">I am sure you will get used to this kind of thing eventually, Shadow. Let us go since we are in a hurry! To get to the capital head west and then follow the road north.</Rin>
    <Explore type="next" id="Timor"></Explore>
  </scene>
  <scene id="9">
    
  </scene>
</Cutscenes>